要是Mickey Mantle(洋基队球员)的击球和这水压一样猛
If Mickey Mantle had this much water pressure,
他绝对能在Maris跟前打出60个本垒打
he'd have hit 60 before Maris.
干完这个 你居然就只知道说棒球和水管?
After that, all you can talk about is baseball and plumbing?
唔 是啊
Mm. Oh.
哦 这场比赛有延长局
Oh, this game's going extra innings.
你觉得你能本垒打?
You think you can knock it out of the park?
- 我肯定行  - 真的?
- Oh, I know I can.  - Oh, yeah?
绝对
Oh, yeah.
你还好吧?
You okay?
真诡异 我打了个寒颤
Yeah, that was weird. I just got a chill.
你打流感疫苗了没? 这几天感冒流行
Did you get your flu shot? There's a bug going around.
我自从1996年来就没生过病了
I haven't been sick since 1996.
快点 我准备好上场了
Now, come on, I'm up to bat,
- 而你...  - 你火烫火烫的
- and you...  - You feel hot.
你也很火辣哟
You look hot.
好了 比赛下雨延期了
Well, this game's rained out.
- 我给你量个体温  - 哦 亲爱的
- I'm taking your temperature.  - Oh, honey.
别 拜托 我们可以继续的
No, please, come on. We can play through this.
好吗? 来 击球手入场
All right? Come on, batter up.
嘴张开
Open up.
蜂群崩溃综合症 Neal
Colony collapse, Neal.
这就是我们需要解决的
That's what we're dealing with here.
数量惊人的意蜂
Apis mellifera are dying off
正在逐渐死亡
in terrifying proportions.
就在Timmy Nolan公园
Timmy Nolan Park.
人们连近地物体都能监测了
People for the awareness of near earth objects,
居然还要解决蜜蜂危机
and now the plight of the honeybees.
全国的农业都得靠这些嗡嗡的小东西
Our nation's agriculture depends on these drones.
没有它们授粉 就没有草莓
Without pollination, there's no strawberries,
- 没有杏仁...  - 没有葡萄?
- no almonds...  - No grapes?
是关于葡萄酒吧?
Is this about wine?
也许吧 你这里够放下三个蜂箱
Maybe. You have room for three hives.
而我一个都不想放到阳台上
That's three more beehives than I want on my terrace.
我说 养蜂在纽约到底合法吗?
I mean, is beekeeping even legal in New York?
五个行政区都允许
Across all five boroughs.
能有什么危险?
I mean, where's the danger?
让人想到杀人蜂
Swarms spring to mind.
不过蜂巢对于走私来说
Although a hive would be a decent hiding spot
是个藏东西的好地方
for contraband.
也是个极好的商机
And an excellent business opportunity.
花粉 蜂胶 还有蜂蜜
Pollen, propolis, and honey
自从古希腊时期以来 就因为医疗功效
have been known for their healing properties
而广为人知
since ancient greece.
克里奥佩特拉(埃及艳后)用牛奶
And Cleopatra bathed
和蜂蜜洗澡 至于我
in milk and honey, and, take it from me,
它们对我的...
what it did for my undercarriage...
行了 先装一个蜂箱
Okay. Start with one hive.
回头见
See you later.
说不定只是过敏
Probably just allergies.
到处都是树上掉的花粉
All those trees dropping pollen everywhere.
我就是喜欢这里的大量树木
I do love how leafy this neighborhood is.
Neal在这里做什么?
What is Neal doing here?
他到底有没有在你身上装定位器呀?
Does he have a tracker on you?
我告诉他我送你去上班
Told him I was walking you to work.
- 早上好 Peter  - 早上好
- Morning, Peter.  - Morning.
早上好 Elizabeth
Elizabeth. Morning.
要我帮你拿吗?
Want me to carry that for you?
- 你在打她的画的主意  - 什么?
- You're casing her art.  - What?
你在打我画的主意?
You're casing my art?
拜托 你们俩有权使用
Please. You guys qualify
- Neal牌家庭亲友套餐  - 我不知道你在说什么
- for the friends and family plan.  - I don't know what that means.
说到家庭...
Speaking of families...
哦 是啊 这个太离奇了
Oh, yeah, that's unbelievable.
本以为自己孩子死了...
Figure your kid's dead...
结果15年后 Patrick出现在门口
Then after 15 years, Patrick shows up at the front door.
一个14岁的孩子是怎么逃过国际追捕的?
How does a 14-year-old evade an international manhunt?
你最后一次看见他是什么时候?
When was the last time you saw him?
我大三前的暑假
The summer before my junior year.
哦 我当时爱上了... 欧洲
Oh, I fell in love with Europe.
我们去了每个城市的博物馆
We were going to museums in every city,
这是我做过的最棒的一次家教
and it was one of the best tutoring jobs I ever had.
可接着他就从瑞士的寄宿学校溜走了
But then he ran away from boarding school in Switzerland,
我再也没听说过他
and I never heard from him again.
有个用早期绘画大师的作品
Must be nice to have a father
迎接你回家的父亲真是太好了
who welcomes you home with old masters.
他想为团聚派对准备大量的新画作
He wanted a lot of new pieces before the homecoming party.
哦 真期待见到他和William
Oh, well, it will be nice to see him
还有 哇哦 Bea那时还是个婴儿
and William, and, wow, Bea was just a baby.
- 当然还有Stanton  - Stanton是谁?
- And of course Stanton.  - Who's Stanton?
男管家 他就像是胶水一样
The butler. He was kind of the glue
- 把一家人凝聚在一起  - 只有一个管家?
- that kept the family together.  - Just one butler?
- 就亿万富翁而言他们很节俭  - 好了 我该走了
- Very frugal for gazillionaires.  - Okay, I'm leaving.
顺便告诉你 我会在画上
Hey, by the way, I'm gonna be putting alarms
装警报器的
on the art.
嗯
Mm.
嗷 不
Aw. No.
- 就亲一口  - 发生什么事了?
- Just one.  - What's going on?
- 你生病了?  - 快走
- You sick?  - Come on.
Mortensen房地产公司案
The Mortensen real estate scandal's
可不会自行解决
not gonna solve itself.
真希望可以
I wish it would.
Burke太太 快进来
Mrs. Burke. Do come in.
Stanton 你还是可以叫我Elizabeth的
Stanton, you still can call me Elizabeth.
不幸的是 我不可以
Unfortunately, I cannot.
日安
Good day.
爸爸 你不能炒了他
Dad, you can't fire him.
我跟你说了 这是侵犯劳动权的
I'm telling you it's a violation of labor rights.
Bea 等你从哈佛法学院毕业了
Bea, when you have graduated from Harvard law,
我们再聊这个不迟
we'll continue this conversation.
可那不是Stanton干的
But Stanton didn't do it.
- Elizabeth  - 啊 William
- Elizabeth.  - William.
- 我不会来得不是时候吧?  - 当然没有
- Is this a good time?  - Of course.
这是我女儿 Bea
This is my daughter Bea.
你还是个婴儿的时候我见过你
I met you when you were a baby.
嗯 我听说过
Mm, I've heard the stories.
而且我不会去法学院的
And I'm not going to law school.
Elizabeth 我得向你道歉
Elizabeth, my apologies.
Bea花了太多时间读小说
Bea spends so much time with her head stuck in novels
现实生活对她来说太刺耳了
that the realities of life are all the harsher.
Stanton的事是真的吗?
Is it true about Stanton?
- 发生什么了?  - 他把我的健康状况
- What happened?  - He leaked the truth
透露给了媒体
about my health to the press.
这令我的生意遭受了损失 也是对我个人的背叛
It was damaging to my business and a personal betrayal.
听到这个消息我很难过
I'm really sorry to hear that.
你怎么样?
How are you?
血糖浓度像市场走势一样忽高忽低
Well, blood sugar spikes like the market,
心跳时速24英里 不过去他的医生吧
ticker's on mile 24, but screw the doctors.
Patrick回家了 我觉得自己一下回到了40岁
Now that Patrick's home, I feel like I'm 40 again.
所以? 他怎么样?
And? How is he?
他可是Patrick
Well, he's Patrick.
你知道 艺术是我们俩唯一的共同点
As you know, art was the only thing we had in common,
希望我们依旧能通过它来沟通
and I'm still hoping that's a way we can connect.
Liz Mitchell 我来了
Liz Mitchell. I'm coming in.
你是Patrick? 哇哦
Patrick? Wow.
- 你长高了  - 蓝头发也没了
- You're taller.  - And lost the blue hair.
我更喜欢这个
I like this better.
你和过去一样美丽
You are as beautiful as ever.
哦
Oh.
是啊 这个害我俩在佛罗伦萨美术学院里被踢了出来
Yeah, that got us kicked out of the accademia in Florence.
哇哦 你的伤疤也还在
Wow, you still have your scar too.
再问你 那匹马叫什么名字?
What was that name of the horse again?
- Cheval Chase  - 没错
- Cheval Chase.  - Yes.
在Stony Hill把我直接甩过了围栏
Threw me clear over the fence at Stony Hill.
那是我第一次以为要失去你了
Mm, and that was the first time I thought I'd lost you.
- 我去看看Bea  - 好的
- I'm gonna go check on Bea.  - Okay.
好了 小子
All right, kid,
我可有很多问题要问你
I've got a lot of questions.
在妈妈死后 我求我爸陪我和Bea
After mom died, I begged dad to let me stay in the city
留在城里
with him and Bea.
你妈妈的事我很抱歉
I was so sad about your mom.
爸爸想让我去读Le Rosey(一所瑞士贵族学校)
Dad wanted me to go to Le Rosey.
- 但我还没准备好  - 这就是你逃跑的原因?
- But I wasn't ready.  - Is that why you ran?
我受够了活在他的条条框框下
I was tired of living on his terms.
你那时只是个孩子
You were just a kid.
- 你怎么做到的?  - 存着零花钱
- How did you do it?  - Saved my allowance.
有天去滑雪 我就从采尔马特滑到切尔维尼亚
On a ski day, I snowboarded from Zermatt to Cervinia,
卖了装备 上了火车
sold my gear, hopped on a train,
再也没回头
and never looked back.
你这一走 你家里人很伤心
You put your family through hell.
为什么回来了?
What made you come back?
因为我爸爸
Dad.
报纸上都在传 说他病了
Rumors that he was sick were all over the papers.
我是为了他回来的 不是为了这种生活
I came back for him, not for this life.
他也在努力
He's trying.
就给我买艺术品?
By buying me art?
这就是他补偿你的方式
It's his way of bonding.
- 随他去吧  - 好吧
- Let him.  - Okay.
我还记得你的喜好
Well, I remember your tastes.
我们有荷兰画家的 巴洛克的
We have Dutch masters, Baroque,
抽象艺术画作
abstract expressionists.
那幅
That one.
毕加索的
The Picasso.
金短号的男子?
The Homme au Cornet?
我是随便放进来的
I put this in as a joke.
还记得索菲亚王妃博物馆吗?
Do you remember the Reina Sofia?
你说"格尔尼卡"画的就是超现实主义的
You called Guernica a bastard child
方块蠢小孩
of cubist-surrealist movement
还说毕加索的作品根本不漂亮
and accused Picasso of crimes against beauty.
我那时还小
I was a kid.
审美观是会变的
Tastes change.
你确定吗?
You sure?
就这幅 我挺喜欢的
Yeah. I love it.
我会让画廊送过来的
Well, I'll have the gallery send it over.
Elizabeth 富豪家怎么样?
Elizabeth. How's Downton Abbey?
我知道听上去可能很奇怪
I know this is gonna sound weird,
但我觉得这个Patrick Wolcott不是真的
but I don't think Patrick Wolcott is Patrick Wolcott.
因为他的眼睛 虽然颜色没错
It's his eyes. They're the right color,
但总觉得不是他
but it doesn't feel like him.
- 你觉得是冒名顶替的?  - 所以是有可能的
- You think he's an imposter?  - So it's possible.
很多人回去冒充富家子弟
Yeah, missing rich kids are a subset.
有人冒充Patty Hearst(美国传媒巨头)的孩子
You got your Patty Hearsts,
John Paul Getty(石油商人)的 还有"天才雷普利"里演的
your John Paul Gettys, talented Mr. Ripleys.
William Wolcott是个完美目标
William Wolcott is a perfect mark.
一个非常病态 但受人同情的目标
A very sick, emotionally fragile mark.
你会查查吗?
Will you look into it?
会 但我得跟Peter说一下...
Yeah. I have to run it by Peter, but...
他怎么样?
How he's holding up?
我去看看
I will find out.
感觉如何?
How are you feeling?
好得不能再好了
Tip-top. Million bucks.
哪怕他是个假的 你觉得
Even if he is a ringer, you're telling me
William Wolcott会认不清自己的儿子?
William Wolcott wouldn't know his own son?
骗子找的就是情感上的弱点
Emotion is a con man's sweet spot.
我有充分理由相信
And I have good reason to believe
这不是真正的Patrick
that that is not the real Patrick.
- 最好充分  - 很充分
- Better be good.  - It is.
- 最好非常充分  - 正是如此
- Better be damn good.  - It is.
什么理由?
Hmm?
你老婆的直觉算数吗?
Does your wife's intuition count?
- El打电话给你了?  - 我跟她说了
- El called you?  - I did say you guys were
让她最好直接找你
on the friends and family plan.
你是为了逃避Mortensen案 精心策划的吧?
Is this some elaborate ruse to avoid the Mortensen case?
这么说就伤感情了 因为如果这是真的
Okay, that hurts my feelings, because we're looking
那就涉及到伪造身份
at potential identity theft, fraud.
一个家族的财产岌岌可危
A family's fortune is at stake,
更别说那笔慈善基金
not to mention the charitable foundation.
有什么根据?
Based on what?
毕加索的画
Pablo Picasso.
他小时候很讨厌毕加索的作品 现在却让Elizabeth买一幅
Kid hated his work, and now he's pushing Elizabeth to buy one.
你想让我就以喜不喜欢毕加索
You want me to launch into an investigation
作为证据立案调查?
based on a Picasso snafu?
Peter 这就跟你突然变成Red Sox队的粉丝一样
Peter, this is like you suddenly becoming a Red Sox fan.
那我得...
I'd have to be...
- 我得...  - 你得怎样?
- I'm...  - You'd have to what?
我得彻底改头换面才会这样
I'd have to be a different person.
谢谢 这里真热
Thank you. It's hot in here.
你看上去不怎么好
Yeah, you really don't look good.
- 你应该回家  - 我不回家
- You should go home.  - I'm not going home.
我没生病 我从来没请过病假
I'm not sick. I've never gone home sick.
除了毕加索 你得给我别的证据
You're gonna have to give me more than Picasso.
还有可疑之处... Wolcott先生辞退了
Also suspicious... Mr. Wolcott fired his butler
用了30年的管家
of over 30 years.
- 好佣人总是很难找  - 或者他就是被陷害的
- Good help is hard to find.  - Or he was set up.
最明智的做法就是赶走
The smart move is to jettison
所有熟悉真正Patrick的人
anyone who intimately knew the real Patrick.
我们得做个DNA测试
We'd need a DNA test.
他父亲没要求做
His father hasn't ordered one.
但Elizabeth去的时候 可以弄根他的头发
But Elizabeth could grab a hair when she's over there.
好吧 我可不能把老婆派去做秘密任务
Okay, I'm not sending my wife in as a secret agent.
- 那派我去  - 你怎么去?
- So send me in.  - How?
Wolcott家族需要个新管家
The Wolcotts need a new butler.
- 我能做  - 做管家?
- I can buttle.  - Buttle?
对啊 就是这意思
Yeah, it's a verb.
Neal Caffrey 为您服务
Neal Caffrey at your service.
--=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
时间轴: pisces夜
翻译: 花孔雀 Mabb 爱鼠影 Wholessness 捞小盐
校对: 爱鼠影
妙警贼探 第五季第5集
除非洗干净了
I don't air dirty laundry.
我不会晾晒脏衣服
I see that it's cleaned.
我不和任何记着说话
I did not speak with the press.
哦 谢谢
Ah. Oh, thank you.
好 你也要一杯吗?
Yes. Would you like one?
抱歉
Excuse me.
从右边开始为客人倒水
One pours from the right.
一直从右边开始 让我来吧
Always from the right. May I?
- 您感觉很热吗 先生?  - 的确
- Are you feeling warm, sir?  - I am.
但我自己有手帕 谢谢
But I've got my own, thanks.
Stanton 我们并不是在讯问你
Stanton, you're not under investigation,
但的确有几个关于Patrick的问题想问你
but we do have questions about Patrick.
你有什么理由相信他不是真的?
Do you have any reason to believe this isn't him?
他当然长大了
He's grown, of course.
但他的行为举止...
But the mannerisms...
如果他是假的 肯定是仔细研究过了
If it isn't, he's a brilliant study.
如果他是假冒的 你应该揭穿他的
If he is a fraud, you could have exposed him.
他是故意陷害你的
He might have sabotaged you.
我们需要确凿证据
We need physical evidence.
如果DNA不匹配
A DNA mismatch would prove
就能证明他是假的
he isn't a Wolcott.
感谢Elizabeth的推荐
Thanks to Elizabeth's recommendation,
William雇了我替补你的位子
William hired me as your replacement.
不好意思 你吗?
Excuse me. You?
Rhett Carlyle 这里的艺术家
Rhett Carlyle, domestic artist.
他在汉普郡的一座城堡里做过管家
He buttled in a castle in Hampshire.
是真的
It's a verb.
我明白
I am aware.
你在汉普郡工作了多久?
How long did you work in Hampshire?
知道他被抓到和公主厮混
Till he was caught with a princess.
是怀疑 我从来没被抓到
Suspected. Never caught.
但证据太奇怪了
But the evidence was overwhelming.
我可没偷银器
I didn't steal the silverware.
管家的工作可不只是
There is more to private service
服侍一群当地贵族
than consorting with the landed gentry.
除了要负责安排侍者和司机的工作
In addition to scheduling valet and chauffeur duties,
当管家必须有非常准确的观察力
one needs to develop an acute sense of observation.
你的鞋是哑光的 不是锃亮的
You wear your Oxfords with a luster, not a shine,
有鞋带
lattice-laced.
腕间的血管突出
Carpal tunnel in your wrist,
可能就是当年倒水留下的
probably from years of pouring from the right.
- 而Peter...  - 恩
- And, Peter... Peter.  - Yes.
肌肉酸痛 嘴唇发干
Muscle fatigue, dry lips,
眼睛流泪 反胃恶心...
watery eyes, nausea...
我很聪明的 这家伙感冒了
I am a brilliant study, and this man has the flu,
所以最好和他保持距离
so you might want to keep your distance.
我一生都在保护这个家族
My life's work has been protecting that family.
我想这点很重要
I want that to matter.
那么就跟我倾囊相授
Then tell me everything I need to know
要怎么照顾好Wolcott一家
about taking care of the Wolcotts.
嘿 Carlyle
Carlyle.
Chauncey准备好去散步了
Chauncey's ready for his walk.
谢谢 Bea小姐
Thank you, Miss Bea.
在92Y有一场"弗兰妮和佐伊"的读书会
There's a reading of Franny and Zooey at the 92nd Street Y.
我给您弄了两张票
I managed to secure you two tickets.
美国中世纪小说
Mid-century American fiction.
我的弱项
My weakness.
Chauncey 我们走
Come on, Chauncey.
- 嘿 Bea  - 嘿 Patrick
- Hey, Bea.  - Hey, Patrick.
打个招呼 Chaunce
Say hi, Chaunce.
兜风怎么样?
How was your ride?
每天早上我都会发现
Every morning there's something else I remember
- 我对这城市的记忆  - 要我帮您拿头盔吗 先生?
- about this city.  - May I take your helmet, Sir?
不用 我要修一下带子
No, I am gonna fix the strap.
要我帮您拿外套吗?
May I take your jacket?
不用 我自己拿
No, I got it.
那您一定想喝点什么吧
You must be thirsty.
我爸觉得还是有仆人好
My father thinks people need servants.
我不觉得 我能照顾好自己
I don't. I can take care of myself.
当然
Of course.
Wolcott先生 时代周刊 先驱报 卫报
Mr. Wolcott, the Times, Herald, and Guardian
都翻到了经济版
all open to the financial section,
您的杏仁酱苋菜土司
and your amaranth toast
已经放在餐厅了
with almond butter's in the dining room.
我的血糖和我一起谢谢你 Carlyle
My blood sugar and I thank you, Carlyle.
- Elizabeth 早上好  - 早上好 William
- Elizabeth, good morning.  - Good morning, William.
- Carlyle  - 早上好 Burke太太
- Carlyle.  - Good morning, Mrs. Burke.
Carlyle真不错
Carlyle is wonderful.
- 你从哪里找到他的?  - 他以前服务的那家主人
- Where did you get him?  - Oh, he actually worked
跟我关系很好
for a family that I'm very close to.
毕加索的画今早到的
The Picasso's coming this morning,
我给您送过来了
and I have a de la tour to show you.
那我们就看看
Let's have a look.
制服很帅 小鬼
Nice uniform, slick.
那家人雇了一组私家侦探...
The family hired a team of private investigators...
跟国际刑警一起...
worked with interpol...
嘿 Peter吃了止痛药?
Hey, Peter, you try acetaminophen?
布洛芬?
Ibuprofen?
是日片还是夜片?
The daytime stuff, the nighttime stuff?
难道是粉色那种?
What about the pink stuff?
好吧
Okay.
- 我是Peter Burke  - 好 就呆在那里
- Peter Burke.  - Yeah, stay in there.
- 想把我甩开?  - 不是!
- You're kicking me out?  - No!
不 不 不... 只是
No, no, no, just...just taking
某种预防措施
the appropriate medical precautions.
好吧
Okay.
能看到地图吧?
You can see the map, right?
没问题吧?
Everything's good?
Patrick乘船离开了德国
Patrick got out of Germany on a barge.
他家里花钱买了不少线索
The family paid a ton in tips.
大部分是在他刚刚逃离学校时支付的
Most of them happened right after he ran from school.
他第一次被发现是在...
He was first spotted at the train station in...
杜塞尔多夫车站
Dusseldorf.
Peter 回家吧
Peter, go home.
我们能应付 好吗?
We got this. Okay?
Caffrey正在办呢
Caffrey is doing his thing.
回家吧
Go home.
哦 领带弄脏了
Oh, I got my tie.
什么也没
Nothing.
比赛到了第八局下半...
And it's the bottom of the eighth inning...
- Neal 嘿  - 你听起来真糟
- Neal, hey.  - You sound terrible.
你在哪?
Where are you?
我在家继续工作
I'm working from home.
"无病假"先生回家啦
Mr. "no sick days" went home.
找到证据没?
Did you get the evidence?
比我们想的困难些
It's gonna be harder than we thought.
我从Patrick杯子上提指纹 他擦掉了
I dusted Patrick's glass. He wiped it.
- 你确定?  - 对
- You sure about that?  - Yeah.
梳子是干净的 牙刷...
Hairbrush is clean. Toothbrush...
剃刀都是清理过的
and razor are sanitized.
处处一尘不染
The surfaces are spotless.
这家伙要么是个洁癖狂...
Either this guy's a total neat freak...
或者活得这么毫无痕迹
Or he has a reason to be living
肯定有他的特殊理由
without leaving a... trace.
他在屋里一直这么无懈可击吗?
Is he this careful all over the house?
他连头盔都不让我拿
Yeah, he wouldn't even hand me his bike helmet.
他非常谨慎
He's careful.
看来Elizabeth是对的
I think Elizabeth's right.
没错 她总是对的
Yeah. She usually is.
- 我得走了  - 他来了?
- I gotta go.  - He onto you?
嗯
Mm.
很不错 小伙子们
It looks great, you guys.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
对不起 Liz
Sorry, Liz.
不是故意吓你的
Didn't mean to scare you.
没事 我正在欣赏这幅毕加索
It's okay. I was just admiring The Picasso.
记得吗? 那些保安警告说如果我对
Remember those guards who threatened to call
立体主义的感叹声音还这么大 他们会报警的
the policia when my manifesto against cubism got too loud?
然后我用全部我会的西班牙语来勾引他们
And I used every spanish word I knew just to charm them.
你答应要是我管住自己的嘴
You promised that we would go to a bullfight
就陪我去看斗牛表演 你骗人
if I kept my mouth shut, which was a lie.
但是我们去了Casa Del Abuelo吃小菜
But we did go to tapas at Casa Del Abuelo,
而那个你喜欢的斗牛士送的小菜
and you let me have a cana, which was sent over
你让我吃了
by that matador who took a shine to you.
他叫Antonnio
Antonio.
姓Paco
Paco.
我全想起来了
It all came back to me.
终于
Eventually.
先生?
Sir?
- Bea小姐  - 能不能
- Miss Bea?  - Would you mind
别这么引人注意?
keeping it down a little bit?
我正在研究家里的事情
I'm working on a genealogy project.
抱歉
Apologies.
我以为是有贼
I mistook it for snooping.
现在咱俩是一伙儿了
Seems we have a pot-kettle situation.
我不评论
No comment.
找到什么有意思的吗?
Find anything interesting?
旅行日记
Um, travel journal.
还算有点意思
Fairly informative.
要知道 我从小听说过不少
You know, I grew up hearing
哥哥的事 如今他活生生地在这里了
all about my brother, and now that he's actually here,
但他告诉的都只是些我知道的事
he's only told me things I already know.
你也许可以问问他的旅行见闻
Maybe you could ask about his travels.
他好像不愿意跟我多谈
It doesn't seem like he really wants to talk to me.
很遗憾 Bea小姐
I'm sorry, Miss Bea.
现在Stanton被解雇了
And now Stanton's fired,
爸爸又病着
and dad's really sick.
很快也会离去
Soon he'll be gone too.
到时候就只剩我和Patrick了
And then it'll just be me and Patrick.
而你不愿跟你不了解的人一起生活
And you don't want to be left with someone you don't know.
你在这里干什么?
Why are you in here?
我想您可以穿这个赴晚宴 先生
I thought you could wear this to dinner tonight, Sir.
告诉我爸 无论他塞多少高档服装
Tell my father no matter how many designer coats
到我的衣柜里
he crams in my closet,
我一件也不会穿
I'm not wearing one.
我能问一下吗? 一个少年如何成功躲过了全球性的搜索?
May I ask, how does a teenager evade an international search?
篡改几位室友的护照
Doctored my dorm mates' passports,
用它们过境 如果需要物资
used 'em to cross borders, and then traded 'em
再把它卖掉
when I needed supplies.
物物交换节省现金 聪明
Bartered to conserve cash. Clever.
美瞳 棒球帽
Colored contacts, a baseball cap.
变换了口音 七月份绕开了波托菲诺?
Switched up your accents and avoided Portofino in July?
我更喜欢圣托里尼
Santorini was more my style.
- 那是您的旅行日记?  - 我的旅行传奇
- Is that your journal?  - Tales of my travels.
好像泡过水
Looks like it got wet.
掉在爱情海了
Dropped it in the aegean.
啊
Ah.
您很幸运 先生
You're lucky, Sir.
- 怎么说?  - 经历了这些
- Why's that?  - After all this,
您父亲还愿意认您
your father will take you back.
不如穿件外套吧
Why not put on a jacket,
让老人家开心点?
make the old man happy?
Carlyle 你没看起来这么简单
Carlyle, you are something else.
祝您晚餐愉快
Enjoy your dinner.
搞到你的指纹了
'Cause I got your print.
亲爱的 药茶
Honey, herbal tea.
好
Okay.
我放了姜
And I got ginger.
和欧斯洛可舒能(一种天然的感冒症状缓解药)
and oscillococcinum.
- 不要啦  - 听话
- Mm-mm.  - Mm-hmm.
不认识的东西我不吃
I don't eat things that I can't say.
我吃这些不认识的东西的时候
At least tell us how you lifted the cuff link
至少告诉我们你是怎么偷到袖扣的
while I eat things I can't say.
PDA大法
PDA.
公开示爱?
Public display of affection?
Elizabeth 可以借一下外套吗?
Elizabeth, can I use your jacket?
好的
Sure.
我恐怕不喜欢这样
I'm not sure I like this.
把这扣在你的左袖口
Clip this to your left sleeve.
这没用的
This is not going to work.
肯定有用
Oh, it's gonna work.
我要从你手腕附近偷走一样东西
I'm gonna steal something right off your wrist.
- 瞧着  - 我瞧着呢
- Watch.  - Oh, I'm watching.
接近技巧(P)
Proximity manipulation.
转移注意力技术(D)
Diversion technique.
注意力控制(A)
Attention control.
接近 转移注意力 注意力控制
Proximity, diversion, attention.
就是PDA
PDA.
还在啊
It's still there.
看你另一只手腕少了什么
From your other wrist.
我早告诉你要偷什么了
I even told you what I was gonna steal.
手表
Wristwatch.
呃 你的手法很温柔
Ugh. You have a gentle touch.
噢 噢 够了啊
Oh, oh, that's enough.
嘿 Jones
Hey, Jones.
好点儿了
Oh, better.
明白 谢谢
Got it. Thanks.
哎 你会变戏法吗? 把坏消息变成
Well, do you have a magic trick that can turn bad news
- 好消息  - 怎么啦?
- into good news?  - Why, what's up?
袖口的指纹很完整
The prints on the cuff link
但它们的主人
were perfect, except they belong to a person
没有犯罪前科
who's never committed a crime.
人们很少让小孩子登记指纹
And it wasn't common to fingerprint kids
所以Patrick小时候的指纹也不在数据库里
when Patrick was younger, so he's not in the database.
我可以把指纹送去总部
I could send it to Quantico
做一个线粒体DNA测试
for a mitochondrial DNA test.
那太浪费时间 我能弄到一些DNA
That takes too long. I can get some actual DNA,
我们在这里测试就行了
and we can run the test here.
把袖扣送回去 试试我的方法
Return the cuff link and try my technique.
GAF法
G.A.F.
- GAF法  - 拿把叉子回来
- G.A.F.  - Grab a fork.
拿... 直接说偷不就完了
Grab... literally steal the silverware.
你是个老古董
You're a cliche.
别放在心上
Get over it.
他病的时候就是这么烦人
He's grumpy when he's sick.
- 躺回去  - 噢
- Lean back.  - Ohh.
- 过得如何?  - 噢 还行
- Hey, what's up?  - Oh, hey. Yeah.
在金色池塘还开心吧?
How's life on golden pond?
哦
Oh.
你开了一瓶布鲁奈罗
And I see you opened the Brunello.
没错 我给你留了...
Oh, yeah, I saved you...
- 请  - 谢谢
- Enjoy.  - Thanks.
嘿 Moz
Moz.
哦 只有这一次 我不是屋里
Oh, for once I'm not the only one in the room
- 唯一嗡嗡嗡的人  - 这声音肯定不止一个蜂巢吧
- with a buzz.  - It's loud for one hive.
我本来可以弄到三个的
I may have acquired three.
自从小Gianetta被抓走了 他老婆就提高警惕了
Skinny Gianetta got nabbed, so his wife put out feelers.
所以 除了要假扮管家
So in addition to me being undercover as a butler
照顾Peter
and taking care of Peter,
我还要照管这一群蜜蜂孤儿们
I'm now the guardian of orphan bees.
猫咪探长得了什么病?
What ails the suit?
还不是现在四处扩散的流感病毒嘛
It's that flu that's going around.
太好啦
That's perfect.
像他那样倔的人正适合
It seems fitting that a man of his persuasion
做我的小白鼠
should be my guinea pig.
内含十八种氨基酸的
18 amino acids packed into an antimicrobial,
抗菌黄酮蜂蜜补品
flavonoid-filled, honey-based tonic
这药能消除你的症状
That will rid you of your symptoms
还能治愈皮肤疣 改善心情
and also cure warts, elevate your mood,
增强性功能
and enhance performance.
别急着感谢我
Thank me later.
- 还是别谢了  - 别
- Or don't.  - Don't.
要我把这个喝下去?
I'm supposed to drink this?
现在喝一支 两小时后再喝一支
One now, the second in two hours,
再隔两小时喝下第三支
and the third within four hours of the first.
我一定是疯了 竟然考虑喝这种东西
Oh, I must be crazy to even consider this.
已经这样了 喝下去还会差到哪里?
Could you feel any worse?
可能不会
Probably not.
我得去Wolcotts家了
I got to get to the Wolcotts.
早点儿好 Peter
Feel better, Peter.
我先不走 观察观察
I'll stay here and observe.
观察什么? 会怎么样?
Observe what? What's gonna happen?
呃 前十五分钟... 呃 我们拭目以待
Well, the first 15 minutes... Well, let's see.
- 就这样定了  - 爸 我不想这样
- Well, it's going to happen.  - Dad, it's not what I want.
我想这样 什么也别说了
It's what I want. Consider that.
我的律师会送过来的
My attorney is sending it over.
- 再来一杯吗?  - 不用了
- May I take your cup?  - No.
谢谢
No.
就没有商量的余地了?
So this conversation's over.
我想是的
In my mind it is.
那我们聊聊别的吧
Let's talk about something else.
你知道吗? 曾经毕加索烧了他的画 就为了取暖
Did you know that Picasso used to burn his own work for warmth?
对 他是这么做过
That's right. He did.
先生
Sir.
啊 弄错了
Oh, this was a mistake.
应该送去给公司经理
It was supposed to go to the business manager.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢 午安
Thank you. Good afternoon.
该喝第二瓶了
Time for vial number two.
Mozzie去哪了?
Where'd Mozzie go?
他得回去看看他的皇后
He needed to check on his queen.
我猜他说的是蜂后
Assuming he meant bee,
- 不过他...  - 还真是说不准
- but with him...  - You never know.
这信是给你的
Ugh. This came for you.
我不能打开 是寄给William Wolcott的
I can't open it. It's for William Wolcott.
但收信人写的是Peter Burke
But it's addressed to Peter Burke.
好吧 恐怕你妻子
You know, I think your wife
得帮你打开 因为你病得不行了
had to open it for you because you're extremely sick.
再说了 没人会知道的
Besides, no one will ever know.
我们可以再封起来
We can just reseal it.
Neal真是把你给带坏了
Neal's a very bad influence on you.
- 好了  - 哇 完好无损
- Oh, yes.  - Wow. That was perfect.
Neal知道Patrick
Neal found out
想要什么了... 一份信托基金
what Patrick's after... a trust fund.
他本该在21岁的时候继承的
He was supposed to inherit it when he was 21.
他们今天在重新整理书面材料
They're redoing the paperwork today.
- 四千万美元  - 是的
- $40 million.  - Yeah.
亲爱的 他拿到这笔钱就会消失的
Honey, if he gets that, he's gonna disappear.
William的心脏怎么承受得住
William's heart can't take that.
我得让他知道事情的真相
I got to let him know what's going on.
不 把William带到联邦调查局
No. Bring William to the FBI.
我要跟他谈谈
I want to talk to him.
我不确定这个Patrick会耍什么花招
I'm not sure what this Patrick is capable of.
他可能是个危险人物
He could be dangerous.
亲爱的 要知道 跟一个父亲谈这个太残酷
Babe, look, this is a hard conversation to have
该找他的朋友来说
with a father, and it needs to come from a friend.
而且 你不要太着急
Besides, you need to take it easy.
不 我等不及了
No, I don't want to take it easy.
- 我感觉好多了  - 很好
- I feel better.  - Well, that's great.
我会让你知道Wolcott家的情况的 好吗?
I'll let you know how it goes at the Wolcotts', okay?
还有 我要你躺下休息
Besides, I want you to lay down.
William 我不是故意
William, I'm not trying
惹你不高兴
to upset you.
嫁给一个联邦调查局探员
Being married to an FBI agent
把你变得疑神疑鬼了
has made you cynical.
该注射胰岛素了 先生
It's time for your insulin, sir.
这跟Peter没任何关系 好吗?
This has nothing to do with Peter, okay?
- 我也被骗了  - 别再说了 Elizabeth!
- I was fooled too.  - I'm offended, Elizabeth!
你们吵得好大声
The whole house can hear you.
- 太荒唐了  - 让Patrick做个血液测试
- This is ridiculous.  - Patrick should have no problem
- 应该没什么难的  - 你不相信我?
- consenting to a blood test.  - You don't believe me?
好吧 现在就抽血吧
Fine. Draw the blood right now.
我不需要 Patrick
I don't need this, Patrick.
但她需要
She does.
不知道还有多少人认为你是个傻瓜呢?
How many others think you're a fool?
我是不会用针头刺我亲生儿子的
I won't stick a needle into my own son.
好吧
Okay.
我自己来
I'll do it.
给你
There.
做测试去吧
Test it.
这座房子跟街道平行
The house is equidistant from the avenues,
但我们不想让他跑那么远
but we don't want him to get that far.
Wolcott宅邸的入口 出口
Entry and exit points
还有楼上的几扇窗户
of the Wolcott residence, upper windows too.
运载车那里我们要安排三名探员
We're gonna have three agents by the utility van,
- 再增派两名内线...  - 三名
- two more undercover...  - Three more.
Peter 你是个病原体
Look, Peter, you're a biohazard.
我的病快好了
I'm on the mend.
我发誓
I swear.
喝了这个就...
And after this...
什么玩意儿?
What is it?
不知道
I don't know.
- Mozzie给我的  - 天啊
- Mozzie gave it to me.  - Oh, God.
这药挺管用的
It works.
我要参加这次行动 我老婆还在里面呢
I'm in on this bust. My wife is in there.
等到一切真相大白了 我们就进去逮捕他
When it all goes down, we'll move in for the arrest.
好孩子 快走 Chauncey
Good boy. Come on, Chauncey.
看来Mozzie的药起作用了
It looks like Mozzie's tincture's working.
我不用上DL名单了
I'm coming off the DL.
棒球用语 伤残名单
Baseball. Disabled list.
你有没有检查他们作亲子测试的实验室?
Did you check out the lab they used to test the blood?
实验室没问题
It's reputable.
我在那儿安插了一个探员 以防Patrick做什么手脚
I put an agent there in case Patrick tried anything.
William让我们去家里取了血样
William had the sample picked up from the house.
我把它封起来亲自交给技术员了
I sealed it and handed it to the technician myself.
就是说Patrick全程没有干涉
So Patrick didn't tamper with it.
没有 但我敢肯定就算DNA测试结果是"不匹配"
No, but I'm sure he has something planned
他也早想好该如何应对了
when the DNA comes back a mismatch.
我想知道会是什么预谋 录下来
I want to know what it is. Audio.
听到吗
Check one, two.
我会保护Elizabeth的
I'll keep an eye on Elizabeth.
快走 Chaunce 快走
Come on, Chaunce. Come on.
真乖
That's a good boy.
一切都顺利吧 Bea小姐?
Everything all right, Miss bea?
血液测试结果出来了
The blood tests are back.
现在就是我们见证事实的时刻了 Carlyle
What we have here, Carlyle, is a real moment of truth.
大家听着 我有事要宣布
Everyone, I have news,
请听好
and you need to hear it.
你们都很辛苦地在准备
You've all been working very hard
周日的宴会
to prepare for the party on Sunday,
但计划有变
But there's been a change of plans.
明天的庆祝取消
The celebration will now take place tomorrow.
我再也等不及了 我要马上迎接
I don't want to wait any longer to welcome home
我的儿子
my son.
我很高兴能回家
I'm so glad to be back.
我本不该让你经历这些的
I shouldn't have put you through this.
- DNA结果是"匹配"  - 同时我想感谢Elizabeth
- The DNA was a match.  - Also I want to thank Elizabeth
为她所做的一切
for all that she's done.
今天是她在这里工作的最后一天
Today is her last day.
William 很抱歉
William, I'm sorry.
你知道我只是关心你和Bea
You know I was just thinking of you and Bea.
我能给我儿子的时间所剩无几了
The days I have left with my son are numbered.
逼他做这件事
Forcing him to do this,
有可能会导致他离开这个家
he could have walked out the door,
而如果果真如此 那都是你造成的
and it would have been your fault.
我会派人把支票给你
I'll send your check.
我做错了什么?
What did I do?
我被炒鱿鱼了
Oh. Well, I'm fired,
你也不用再假扮管家了
and you don't have to be a butler anymore.
我还不能离开
I can't just leave.
我想看看那个法国女仆到底如何
Maybe I'll see how French that maid really is.
Liz 我试图劝父亲来着
Liz. I tried to talk to my father,
但你知道的 他非常固执
but you know how stubborn he is.
他很生我的气
Well, he's upset with me,
可以理解
and I can understand that.
我已经遛过Chauncey了
I already took Chauncey on his walk.
好吧 不过我听到他咳嗽
Oh. Well, I heard him coughing.
得带他去看兽医
I'm gonna take him to the vet.
要是他不舒服
Well, if he's not feeling well,
- 就不该走着去  - 又不远
- he shouldn't walk.  - It's not far.
他要是连呼吸都困难就算远了
It is if he can't breathe.
别担心 我开车送他们
Don't worry. I'll drive them.
我去开车
I'll get the car.
再见 Burke太太
Good day, Mrs. Burke.
保重 Patrick
Take care, Patrick.
你也保重 Liz
You too, Liz.
在这等着
Wait here,
不许离开半步
and don't move the car.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
Peter 听着 Patrick很讨厌那条狗
Hey, Peter. Patrick hates the dog.
现在却送他去看兽医
Now he's bringing it to the vet.
我都听到了 你身上有监听设备
I heard. You're wired.
你从我的手下Godfrey摇身一变成了"艾斯·文图拉"
You've gone from my man Godfrey to Ace Ventura.
"艾斯·文图拉" 电影"神探飞机头"主角 一位专与动物打交道的宠物侦探
我是要跟你说 他有新动作
I'm telling you, he's got another move.
Neal 记得按兵不动
Neal, recon only.
发现任何线索 立刻告知我
You find anything, you pull me in.
没问题
You got it.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
我身体好了 完全好了
I feel good. Really good.
太好了 你和Wolcott家的狗身体一样好
Great. You and the Wolcotts' dog.
Patrick是去为自己看兽医的
Patrick went to the vet for himself.
我看到那个技术人员从他的胳膊这里
I watched the tech remove something from his arm
- 取出了什么  - 塑料的?
- right here.  - Plastic?
- 是的  - 像一截血管?
- Yeah.  - Look like a vein?
不知道 大概是这个东西的三分之二长
I don't know. It was about 2/3 this size.
是彭罗斯引流
That's a Penrose drain.
外科手术装置 可植入体内以排出液体
佛罗里达州有个案子里...
There was a case in Florida...
一个人植入了这样一根
a guy implanted one
来蒙混DNA测试
to fool a DNA test.
装有别人的血液?
Filled with someone else's blood?
没错
Yeah.
难怪Patrick要自己抽血
That's why Patrick drew his own.
血液还是新鲜的
This blood was fresh.
也就意味着真正的Patrick Wolcott
Which means 48 hours ago
在48小时之前仍然活着
the real Patrick Wolcott was alive.
而且就在纽约
And in New York.
你看 咱们干得不错
You know, we're kind of good at this.
怎么了?
What?
William打算明天签下信托基金
William's signing over the trust fund tomorrow.
而一旦冒牌Patrick得手...
And once fake Patrick gets what he wants...
他就不需要让真的Patrick活下去了
he won't have any reason to keep the real Patrick around.
没错
No.
我们抓了那个兽医
We pulled in the vet tech.
当然了 他概不承认彭罗斯引流的事
Of course he denies implanting a Penrose drain.
我们搜查了现场 没有发现人造血管
We searched the property. No signs of the tubing.
那我们把他扣着 免得他跑去给Patrick通风报信?
We're holding him on suspicion so he can't tip Patrick off?
最好如此
You better believe it.
可是 没有家里人的允许
Well, we won't get a warrant for another DNA testing
我们搞不到授权再对其进行一次DNA测试
without permission from the family.
咱们干嘛不干脆把那个人渣抓来
Why don't we just grab the bastard
当面告诉他我们知道人造血管的事了?
and tell him we know about the drain?
我也想啊 可是咱们没有筹码
Tempting, but we have no leverage.
那就搞些筹码来
So let's get some leverage.
- 怎么弄?  - 嗯
- How do we do that?  - Hmm.
毕加索
Picasso.
是啊 是啊 毕加索
Yeah, yeah, Picasso.
好了 我们这位冒牌做足了功课
All right, our imposter learned everything he could
尽可能详尽地了解了Patrick的一生
about Patrick's life.
但他对Elizabeth那个毕加索的事并不知情
But he didn't know Elizabeth's Picasso story,
也就是说他并非无所不知
which proves he doesn't know everything.
是啊 而且他事先不知道的事情
Yeah, and he doesn't know
现在一定是不知道的
what he doesn't know.
我们要问他
We need to ask him
一些他认为只有真的Patrick才会
something that he thinks only the real Patrick
- 知道答案的事情  - 便可以促使他
- knows the answer to.  - And give him a reason
去寻找那个答案
to get that answer.
Elizabeth刚问过他毕加索的事...
Elizabeth asks him about Picasso...
第二天早上他就突然都知道了
the next morning he knows everything.
自行车出行
The bike rides.
他每天早上都骑自行车出去 每次都是一个小时
He goes on one every morning. It's always for an hour.
他一定是这样来维持Patrick活着的
That's got to be how he's keeping Patrick alive.
而且问到了毕加索那件事
And how he got the Picasso story.
- 还有血样  - Jones 在那附近
- And the blood.  - Jones, get a radius
设下包围圈... 开车 骑车 步行 怎么都行
set up in op... car, bike, foot, whatever.
只要确保无论如何我们不会跟丢他
Make sure we stay on him wherever he goes.
明白
Gotcha.
Patrick离开了15年
Patrick was gone for 15 years.
他应该不是一开始就结识了这个冒牌
He probably didn't meet the imposter right away.
他从寄宿学校逃走之后
The first time he was spotted after he ran away
首次被人看到是在杜塞尔多夫(德国西北部城市)
from boarding school was at Dusseldorf.
就在这个时候Leo Kovak出现了
And that's where Leo Kovak comes in.
谁是Leo Kovak?
Who is Leo Kovak?
这问题要麻烦冒牌Patrick去解答了
He's the reason fake Patrick has to get the answer.
谁是Leo Kovak?
Who is Leo Kovak?
让我当Leo Kovak?
I'm Leo Kovak?
你是一个气急败坏的克罗地亚人
You are a very angry Croatian.
你为Von Kesslers工作
You work for the Von Kesslers,
而你想知道在杜塞尔多夫到底发生了什么
and you want to know what the hell happened in Dusseldorf.
在杜塞尔多夫发生了什么?
What happened in Dusseldorf?
你... 你得演得再像一点
It's... it's got to be more convincing.
- 杜塞尔多夫那次到底怎么回事?  - 没什么
- What happened in Dusseldorf?  - Nothing.
但Patrick不知道这点
But Patrick doesn't know that.
克罗地亚人发明了领带
Croatians invented neckties,
我敢肯定你的衣橱里有那么一条
and I'm sure you've got something in your closet
能完美演绎一名暴怒的巴尔干半岛人
that screams enraged balkan.
我演不来克罗地亚人
I can't do Croatian.
我要演波兰人
I'm going Polish.
咱们去找条合适的领带吧
Let's pick out that tie.
Kovak先生来这里见您
Mr. Kovak is here to see you.
我是Von Kesslers的朋友
I'm a friend of the Von Kesslers.
当然 Von Kesslers
Of course. The Von Kesslers.
自从杜塞尔多夫一面已经过去很久了
It's been a while since Dusseldorf.
谢谢你 Carlyle
Thank you, Carlyle.
我一直通过报纸关注你和你的故事 Patrick
I followed you and your story in the papers, Patrick.
我们就是这样找到你的
That's how we found you.
抱歉 我...
I'm sorry. Do I...
你应该为你的所作所为追悔莫及
You should be sorry for what you did.
- 先生 我不太明白  - 别跟我装傻
- Sir, I don't understand.  - Don't play stupid.
别开始哭哭啼啼的
Don't start crying.
Von Kesslers雇了我来处理这个问题
The Von Kesslers pay me to handle their problems.
我该付给他们多少钱来平息这份不愉快?
Is there any way I can pay them for this inconvenience?
你以为你的所作所为能用几个子儿来衡量吗?
You think you can put a price on what you did?
花点小钱就能摆平?
That money can make this go away?
想都别想 他们要的是一个答复
No. They want answers.
来自主厨的款待
Compliments of the chef.
还需要什么吗 先生?
Anything else, sir?
一支钢笔 还有纸
A pen and something to write.
联系我 只要你合作 我们就能让杜塞尔多夫的事过去
Call me. We can make Dusseldorf go away.
你要是不合作 那就只好今晚的派对上见了
But if you don't, I'll see you at your party tonight.
我自己出去就行
I'll show myself out.
恕我直言 先生...
If I may, sir...
那家伙不像是在虚张声势
that threat didn't sound hollow.
我得出去骑会儿车
I'm going for a bike ride.
请尽情享用新鲜空气
Enjoy the fresh air.
他出了116号街的晨兴公园
He's exiting the park at morningside and 116th.
我跟上他了
I've got him.
坐在这车里我都不会觉得你是个联邦探员
I wouldn't peg you for a fed in this car.
路障都设好了
Perimeter is all set.
我们要把Patrick抓个现行
We'll pinch Patrick at the location.
我们等的时候
While we're waiting,
我能不能...
may I...
多谢 Leo
Thanks, Leo.
向北朝曼哈顿区去了 交接班
North on Manhattan. Handing off.
听听!
Listen to that!
114号街 急转弯
Hard turn, 114th.
探员倒下! 目标跟丢了!
Agent down! We lost the suspect!
Neal 我来开
Neal, get out.
我是个管家 专门训练过的
I'm a butler. I'm trained for this.
叫救护车来
Call an ambulance.
所有探员到第一大道和114号街会和
All agents to first avenue and 114th street.
Burke探员和Caffrey正赶过去
Agent Burke and Caffrey are en route.
二队看到他了 在西边116号街
Team two has him. West on 116th.
这就是116号街
This is 116th.
Neal啊
Neal.
- Neal  - 闭上眼睛
- Neal.  - Don't look.
我忍不住要看
I have to look. I can't help it.
找到他了
There he goes.
在晨兴公园和115街角落
Lost sight of the suspect
失去嫌疑人踪影
at the corner of morningside and 115th.
这管家大学培训得真到位
That must be some butler college.
他把Patrick关哪里了?
Where's he keeping Patrick?
他刚才就在那儿 一定就在附近
He was just here. Got to be somewhere close.
好了 我们得一家一户找
All right, we're gonna have to go door to door.
一个队负责这栋楼 那边
I want a team on this building, down there,
另一个队负责街对面
and a team across the street.
二队 我们走
Team two, let's go.
- 嘿 Peter  - 诶 有什么头绪?
- Hey, Peter.  - Yeah, what do you have?
可能扯得有些远
This may be a long shot,
但Patrick说过他把他的
but Patrick said he dropped
航行日志掉在爱琴海里过
his travel journal in the Aegean.
未必是爱琴海 不管怎样咱们来看看
Not exactly the Aegean, but let's have a look.
最后问你一遍 杜塞尔多夫
For the last time, Dusseldorf.
- 到底怎么回事?  - 在杜塞尔多夫
- What the hell happened? - Nothing happened
- 什么也没发生  - Von Kesslers的人气坏了
- in Dusseldorf.  - The Von Kesslers are pissed,
这个叫Kovaks的来追杀你
and this Kovaks guy is coming after you.
这些人我一个都不认识
I don't know any of these people.
好吧
Okay, fine.
很好
Fine.
只能来硬的了
We'll do this the hard way.
要是你不把电击枪放下
The hard way is what's gonna happen if you don't
的确是要来硬的了 Peter Burke 联邦调查局的
put that taser down. Peter Burke, FBI.
把他铐上
Cuff him.
- 我才不是什么管家  - 走
- I'm not a butler.  - Let's go.
都没事了 好吗?
Everything's gonna be okay, all right?
- Patrick  - 爸爸
- Patrick.  - Dad.
我太想把他当做你了
I wanted him to be you so much,
所以自欺欺人
I let myself believe.
我对不起你
I'm sorry.
是我对不起你们 让他搅乱了你们的生活
I'm sorry I let him into our lives.
Liz啊
Liz.
嗨
Hi.
是Bea吧?
Bea?
你知道吗
You should know,
我都习惯了是家里的独女了
I'm used to being an only child.
Patrick和Keith... 那是他的真名...
Patrick and Keith... that's his real name...
在锡拉结识(爱琴海岛名)
met on Santorini.
别人都说他俩长得跟亲兄弟似的
People said they could pass for brothers.
Patrick决定回家后
When Patrick decided to come home,
Keith提出陪他一起回来
Keith offered to come with him.
他控制住了Patrick
He took Patrick hostage,
读了他的日志
read his journals.
偷天换日
That man stole his life.
现在又换回来了
And now he's got it back again.
- 多亏了你  - 多亏了我们
- Thanks to you.  - Thanks to us.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
想不想... 想不想来点棒球运动?
Are you up for some... some baseball?
- 夜场?  - 是啊
- A night game?  - Yeah.
接着上次的来
I figured we could pick up where we left off.
我应该可以...
I could probably...
哦 不
Oh, no.
该死
Damn it.
我给Mozzie打电话
I'll call Mozzie.
等等 等等 让我想想
Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
既然你已经得过这个流感
If you've had this flu already,
那就没事了
I think we're safe.